[
  {
    "question": "Which HTML5 element should contain important links for navigating a website?",
    "id": 1,
    "topic": "html",
    "choices": {
      "a": "<li>",
      "b": "<ul>",
      "c": "<header>",
      "d": "<nav>"
    },
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which HTML5 element should contain important information about what page you are on and the topic of the page?",
    "id": 2,
    "topic": "html",
    "choices": {
      "a": "<li>",
      "b": "<ul>",
      "c": "<header>",
      "d": "<nav>"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which JavaScript variable declaration is used when the assigned value is likely to change?",
    "id": 3,
    "topic": "javascript",
    "choices": {
      "a": "let",
      "b": "var",
      "c": "variable",
      "d": "const"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which term in JavaScript can be used to describe a declared variable that has not yet been given a value?",
    "id": 4,
    "topic": "javascript",
    "choices": {
      "a": "null",
      "b": "undefined",
      "c": "typeError",
      "d": "NaN"
    },
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which selector could refer to an html element with the class of 'sm-col'?",
    "id": 5,
    "topic": "css",
    "choices": {
      "a": "#sm-col",
      "b": ".sm, .col",
      "c": "[class~=col]",
      "d": ".sm_col"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Setting an element height to '10vh' bases the height calculation on _________",
    "id": 6,
    "topic": "css",
    "choices": {
      "a": "viewfinder height",
      "b": "viewport width",
      "c": "visible height",
      "d": "viewport height"
    },
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which HTML5 property can be used for custom data?",
    "id": 7,
    "topic": "html",
    "choices": {
      "a": "data-",
      "b": "-data-",
      "c": "data=",
      "d": "custom"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which HTML5 tag is used to define 'independant, self-contained content' within a web page?",
    "id": 8,
    "topic": "html",
    "choices": {
      "a": "<section>",
      "b": "<main>",
      "c": "<aside>",
      "d": "<article>"
    },
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following snippets does not result in a return value of 8?",
    "id": 9,
    "topic": "javascript",
    "choices": {
      "a": "8**1",
      "b": "Math.pow(16, .75)",
      "c": "2 * 2 * 'two'",
      "d": "2**+'3'"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these statements is NOT true of browser-side JavaScript?",
    "id": 10,
    "topic": "javascript",
    "choices": {
      "a": "JavaScript can be used for functional programming.",
      "b": "JavaScript can be used for file reading and writing on client machines.",
      "c": "JavaScript does not require frameworks or libraries to be used.",
      "d": "Though not class-based, JavaScript is an Object-Oriented Programming Language."
    },
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "If we want define style for an unique element, then which css selector will we use ?",
    "id": 11,
    "topic": "css",
    "choices":{
      "a":"id",
      "b":"class",
      "c":"text",
      "d":"name"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "If we don't want to allow a floating div to the left side of an element, which css property will we use ?",
    "id": 12,
    "topic":"css",
    "choices":{
      "a":"margin",
      "b":"clear",
      "c":"float",
      "d":"floating"
    },
    "answer":"b"
  },
  {
    "question":"Suppose we want to arragnge five nos. of DIVs so that DIV4 is placed above DIV1. Now, which css property will we use to control the order of stack?",
    "id":13,
    "topic":"css",
    "choices":{
      "a":"d-index",
      "b":"c-index",
      "c":"s-index",
      "d":"z-index"
    },
    "answer":"d"
  },
  {
    "question":"an we align a Block element by setting the left and right margins ?",
    "id":14,
    "topic":"css",
    "choices":{
      "a": "yes, it's possible",
      "b":"no, it's not possible"
    },
    "answer":"b"
  },
  {
    "question":"If we want to wrap a block of text around an image, which css property will we use ?",
    "id":14,
    "topic":"css",
    "choices":{
      "a":"wrap",
      "b":"push",
      "c":"float",
      "d": "align"
    },
    "answer":"c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we define the text direction via css property ?",
    "id": 15,
    "topic":"css",
    "choices":{
      "a": "yes",
      "b": "no"
    },
    "answer":"a"
  },
  {
    "question":"If we want to show an Arrow as cursor, then which value we will use ?",
    "id":15,
    "topic":"css",
    "choices":{
      "a":"pointer",
      "b":"default",
      "c":"arrow",
      "d":"arr"
    },
    "answer":"b"
  },
  {
    "question":"If we want to use a nice looking green dotted border around an image, which css property will we use?",
    "id":16,
    "topic":"css",
    "choices":{
      "a":"border-color",
      "b":"border-decoration",
      "c":"border-style",
      "d":"border-line"
    },
    "answer":"c"
  },
  {
    "question":" Which of the following properties will we use to display border around a cell without any content?",
    "id":17,
    "topic":"css",
    "choices":{
      "a":"empty-cell",
      "b":"blank-cell",
      "c":"noncontent-cell",
      "d":"void-cell"
    },
    "answer":"a"
  },
  {
    "question":"What should be the table width, so that the width of a table adjust to the current width of the browser window?",
    "id":18,
    "topic":"css",
    "choices":{
      "a":"640 pixels",
      "b":"100%",
      "c":"full-screen",
      "d":"1024px"
    },
    "answer":"a"
  },
  {
    "question":"How can we write comment along with CSS code ?",
    "id":19,
    "topic":"css",
    "choices":{
      "a":"/* a comment */",
      "b":"// a comment //",
      "c":"/ a comment /",
      "d":"<' a comment'>"
    },
    "answer":"a"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which css property you will use if you want to add some margin between a DIV's border and its inner text?",
    "id":20,
    "topic":"css",
    "choices":{
      "a":"spacing",
      "b":"margin",
      "c":"padding",
      "d":"inner-margin"
    },
    "answer":"c"
  }
  

]

